

ALİ EREN KAYHAN

JUNIOR UNITY GAME DEVELOPER 2D-3D

CAREER OVERVIEW

Highly motivated game programmer with 1 year of experience creating indie for PC. Developed The Virus which was a horror game downloaded 140 times and viewed 856 times, and Wer Ist Der Mörder which was an instructional game downloaded 20 times and viewed 86 times, and Atölye which was an instructional game downloaded 2 times and viewed 19 times. These games are made with Unity. Moreover, I have written 29 blogs about different topics on my personal website. Also, I have been working on my start-up project.

The skills I've been able to gain and hone in on during my education:

- Working with a team
- Team management
- Documentation
- Project management
- German-language skills at A2
- English-language skills at B2
- Starting a Start-up

You can learn more about me by visiting my personal website. (https://alierenkayhan.github.io/).

PROJECTS

Creating University Network System In Cisco Packet Tracer

Instructional Blog | Networking

- Creating university network topologies and imitating modern computer networks.
- Team works

Atölye

Instructional Game | Mathematics | Unity 2D Game | Github & itch.io

- Creating a 2D instructional game in Unity
- Teaching Grade 6 Mathematics Angles and Area Measurement
- Work as a game developer.

Wer Ist Der Mörder?

Instructional Game | German | Unity 2D Game | Indie Game | Github & itch.io

- Creating a 2D instructional game in Unity
- Teaching one of the German Grammar rules, "Relativsätze im Nominative".
- Work as a game developer

The Virus

Horror Game | Unity 3D Game | Indie Game | Github & itch.io

- Creating a 3D instructional game in Unity.
- Solo game developer

Unity AR:

Unity AR & Blog

• Creating Unity AR.

SQL Pizza Company Database

Database | Mssql & Blog

- Preparing class diagram.
- Creating a database.

VEX Robotics

Programming Robots | VEX Robotics & Blog

• Programming a robots in stem labs.

Ardunio

Ardunio & Blog

• Designing and manufacturing single-board microcontrollers and microcontroller kits for building digital devices

Intelligent Life in the Universe

Physics | Blog

• Researching intelligent life in the universe

Energy plan for German

Sustainable Development | Blog

• Designing energy optimism and algorithms for german

LooneytUneS

Instructional Game | Teaching C programming | Scratch Games & Blog

- Creating a 2D instructional game in Unity
- Teaching C programming to beginners
- Work as a game developer.



ALİ EREN KAYHAN

JUNIOR UNITY GAME DEVELOPER 2D-3D

LANGUAGE

- German A2
- English B2

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Asp.Net MVC Core
- C#
- SOL
- Unity 2D-3D game development

REACH ME:

- **Phone:** 0530 964 98 44
- Email: ali erenbatman@hotmail.com
- Personal Website: alierenkayhan.github.io/
- LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-eren-kayhan/

- **Itch.io:** alierenkayhan.itch.io/
- **Github:** github.com/Alierenkayhan
- Blog: https://alierenkayhanbouncet.blogspot.c om/

EXPERIENCE

MyEdu Startup Project

Co-founder | 2020- Present

- Work on Start-up project.
- Developing a new modern and user-friendly LMS system with Asp.net MVC Core, CSS, SQL, HTML, Bootstrap, Javascript

Ted Talks Translator

Translator | As a volunteer | 2022- Present

Translating Ted Talks videos from English to Turkish as a volunteer

EduTech - Boğaziçi University Education and **Technology Community**

Team member | 2020 - Present

- Responsible for the club logo design
- Responsible for the club activity's poster design

Compec - Boğaziçi University Informatics Club

Team member | September 2017 - 2018

- Responsible for contact with Airbar firm and Techsummit 18.
- Responsible for registering and helping people.
- Responsible for helping people in the Insider Firm Tour and taking photos.

Yıldız Teknik University

Internship | September 2016 - November 2016

- For vocational High School.
- Internship under the control of Assistant Professor Doctor Ziya Cihan Tayşi.
- Responsible for arranging cable of laboratory
- Responsible for making a design plan for a laboratory in adobe fireworks.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Boğaziçi University

Computer and Instructional Technologies teaching (english) | 2017- Still

- Compec Club, Edutech Club, and Boun Atletizm Club
- BÜMED Mentor-Mentee Program 2022 As a mentee and my mentor is Gökhan Öncü.
- Career Counseling Program by Boğaziçi University Career Center 2022 - As a mentee and my Career Counselor is Nilhan Fidan.

Tuncay Azaphan A.T.M. HIGH School

Information Technologies / Web Programming | 2012 - 2017

- Grade average: 86,78
- Team member in Basketball, Chess, Knowledge Contest, Shot Put

HOBBY

- 10 bronze, 6 silver, and 2 gold medals from sports.
- Judo (2. dan judo black belt, 1. level judo assistant coach, more than 10 years)
- Basketball
- Chess
- Saz playing
- Solving the Rubik's Cube and Megamix
- Indie Unity Game Development